In this American English pronunciation video,
在这段美式英语发音视频中，
we're going to learn how to make the NG consonant sound.
我们将学习如何发 NG 辅音音。
To make this sound,
要发出这个音，
the jaw drops a little bit.
下巴稍微放低。
Nng.
Nng。
The lips part and the back part of the tongue stretches all the way up to the soft palate.
嘴唇分开，舌头的后部伸展到软腭。
The tongue tip is forward.
舌尖向前。
Because the soft palate is lowered,
因为软腭降低，
air comes up through the nasal passages.
空气通过鼻腔流出。
This makes it a nasal consonant.
这使得它成为一个鼻音辅音。
You can feel the vibration in your nose.
你可以在鼻子里感受到振动。
Nng.
Nng。
There are only three nasal sounds in American English.
美式英语中只有三个鼻音。
Nng,
Nng，
ng,
ng，
ng.
ng。
Let's study it up close and in slow motion.
让我们近距离慢动作学习它。
A relaxed, lowered jaw.
放松的、降低的下巴。
Since this sound is made at the back of the mouth,
由于这个音是在口腔后部发出的，
it's hard to get a clear picture of it.
很难清楚地看到它。
The tongue lifts in the back while the tip stays down and forward.
舌头在后部抬起，而舌尖保持向下和向前。
The word ring.
单词 ring。
The tongue lifts in the back while the tip stays down and forward.
舌头在后部抬起，而舌尖保持向下和向前。
Lips are relaxed.
嘴唇放松。
The word along.
单词 along。
Since the tongue is low for the vowel before,
由于元音前的舌头较低，
it's easier to see the tongue lift in the back.
更容易看到舌头在后部抬起。
And now it's lifted in the back with relaxed lips.
现在舌头在后部抬起，嘴唇放松。
The word finger.
单词 finger。
Again, the tongue lifts in the back while the tip stays down and forward.
再次，舌头在后部抬起，而舌尖保持向下和向前。
At the beginning.
在开头。
The NG consonant.
NG 辅音。
Ring.
Ring。
Along.
Along。
Finger.
Finger。
Example words.
示例单词。
Repeat with me.
跟我重复。
Anger.
Anger。
Nng.
Nng。
Anger.
Anger。
Song.
Song。
Nng.
Nng。
Song.
Song。
Wing.
Wing。
Nng.
Nng。
Wing.
Wing。
English.
English。
Nng.
Nng。
English.
English。
Single.
Single。
Nng.
Nng。
Single.
Single。
Beginning.
Beginning。
Nng.
Nng。
Beginning.
Beginning。